videoschoolonline.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy & FTC Disclaimer - Video School Online

**PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY.**

This Privacy Policy applies to the Video School Online websites and related subdomains, mobile applications, and media (our “website”) managed by Video School Online, Inc. (“Video School Online”, “we”, or “us”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using any information we collect through your use of the website responsibly. This Privacy Policy addresses our use and disclosure of the information we collect from you.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to accessing or using our website or our services. If you have any questions, please contact as at:  _support@videoschoolonline.com_.

**The Information We May Collect**

Our primary purpose in collecting information from or about you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Depending on the manner in which you our website or our services, we collect information about you that we deem necessary for providing services and features that optimize, secure, and ease your user experience.

_Personal Information (“PII”)_ : Video School Online may collect and process information that could be directly associated with you, without the aid of additional information; information such as your full name, company name where applicable, user name and password, phone number, email address, billing or mailing address, or credit/debit card information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register for an account; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.

_Payment Information_ :* *For the purposes of billing Video School Online Plan subscription fees and Video School Online powered course enrollment fees that are processed through Video School Online’s payment gateways, we may request your credit card and certain contact information, such as a billing address. We retain credit card information internally for the purpose of all payment processing related to our services.

_Third Party Payment Processors_ :* *Payments processed via Custom Payment Gateways by third parties like PayPal and Stripe are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of those payment gateways and are not accessible or controlled by Video School Online. For payments processed via Video School Online Payment and Custom Payment Gateways, we receive information related to the payment status of your account; this information includes, but is not limited to, your payment card type and last four digits, postal code, country of origin, and payment expiration date. For additional information, we recommend that you review the payment processor’s Privacy Policy.

_Information from Third Party Platforms_ : You may allow our website to interact with one or more third party social networks or platforms (such as Facebook), which will provide data about you to us (“Platform(s)”). The information you allow Video School Online to access varies by Platform, and it is affected by the privacy settings you and those that you are connected with establish while using such Platforms. Platforms are operated, controlled, and maintained by third parties that are not operated, controlled, or maintained by Video School Online. We recommend that you read the terms of use or service and privacy policies of those Platforms to understand how they collect and treat your data and what data they might share with us or other third parties.

_Demographic and Usage Data (Non-Personal Information)_ : Video School Online may collect information through the use of cookies, HTML5 local storage, and other similar technologies. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your web browser on your hard drive. Video School Online may set and access cookies on your computer or wireless device to track and store preferential information about you. We may gather anonymous information about Users through cookie technology on an individual and aggregate level. Such information is used within Video School Online internally and is only shared with third party advertisers, if any, on an aggregated or non-personally identifiable basis. You may opt out of receiving cookies from our website by following the instructions in your web browser. Note, however, that deleting cookies or directing your browser to refuse them may limit your ability to use certain portions of our website that require cookies to function. Video School Online gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, operating system, and other usage information about the use of our website, including a history of the pages you view.

*Non-Personal Information. *Web Beacons, also known as pixel tags and clear GIFs, (“Web Beacons”), are electronic images that allow a website to access cookies and help track marketing campaigns and general usage patterns of visitors to those websites. Web Beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as cookie numbers, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the Web Beacons are placed. No PII about you is shared with third parties through the use of Web Beacons on our website. However, through Web Beacons, we may collect general information that will not personally identify you, such as: Internet browser, operating system, IP address, date of visit, time of visit and path taken through the website. Video School Online may also collect other Non-Personal Information as visitors browse our website, such as the web traffic, what pages are visited, from where visitors come, and other demographic information, such as age, gender, and search habits.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We may use the information we collect for a number of purposes. We may use it to respond to your inquiries and otherwise correspond with you, to process transactions that you request, to maintain accounts, such as your Video School Online account, to preserve the security and integrity of our website and services, to conduct market research or surveys, and to administer, review, and/or improve the content of our website and services. We may also use the information to communicate with you, and make recommendations, about Courses and other services that we think may be of interest, or to address refund, chargebacks, payment or copyright disputes.

Video School Online may use Web Beacons internally to count visitors and recognize visitors through cookies. We may compile this Non-Personal Information to enable statistical analysis of our services that would be used internally or with external assistance to make improvements to our website and services.

Video School Online may use and share Non-Personal Information we collect with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our website or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine Non-Personal Information we collect with additional Non-Personal Information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-personal information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors. For example, we may engage a third party acting on our behalf to collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system) when you use our website and other websites you may access during your Internet browsing session, or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized advertisements or content. For more information regarding your choices about how third parties collect information about you on our website see the section titled Do-Not-Track Procedures below.

Except as stated above, Video School Online may disclose any of your information, which in some cases includes PII, in the following situations:

1.With your consent. Video School Online may transmit your PII to a third party when you give us express permission to do so. For example, this may occur when we complete a transaction on your behalf or at your request.

2.With our authorized service providers. Video School Online may share your PII with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include processing credit card payments, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to PII needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

3.With our business partners. When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our website, we may share PII with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.

4.In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business; a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale; or in the event of bankruptcy. If another company acquires Video School Online, that company will take on all responsibility for the information we collect, including PII, and it will assume all rights and obligations with respect to that information. Should this happen, the acquiring company may implement its own policies with respect to your information.

5.Video School Online may use information available on the performance and availability of Video School Online powered websites for advertising purposes on Video School Online.com, and external outlets. Additionally, Video School Online may use the information available within a Student’s account for promotional activities unless and until the Student informs us that they no longer wish to receive any promotional materials.

6.If we are required to disclose information by law. Video School Online may be obligated to disclose a User’s personal information, if directed by a court of law or other governmental entity. Without limiting the foregoing, we reserve the right to disclose such information where we have a good faith basis to believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law; (b) protect and defend Video School Online’s rights and property, or safety of Video School Online, our users, our employees, or others; (c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website and/or Services and/or to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements or policies; and/or (d) protect your personal safety or property or that of the public. In the event that your information is disclosed, we will comply with the law and make commercially reasonable efforts to notify you.

Please keep in mind that all of the information that you disclose or content that you post in your user profile, forum posts, comments, or other public portions of our website becomes public information. Because this information is publicly available, we cannot control how others treat it so we ask all Users to exercise care in deciding what information they chose to share. If you terminate your Video School Online account, we may retain your PII for administrative purposes but will not publicly or share it in any other way. This does not mean that we will scrub your posts from our publicly available information.

**New Uses of Information**

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should visit our website periodically and review our policies.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your data for a period of up to three (3) months (or the maximum time required by law) after your account (a) has been cancelled, (b) is on a credit hold for nonpayment, or (c) ends after a trial period. After this time, the information will be permanently removed from our servers and no one will be able to access it. Your personal information such as your email, name, type of account you had, and payment history will remain on file for a period of up to ten (10) years, or the maximum time required by law, to comply with government regulations. Again, this does not mean that we will scrub your posts from our publicly available information.

**Access to Your Information**

Video School Online will provide you with access to PII that you submitted to Video School Online for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. If you believe that any PII we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, or to have Video School Online completely remove your PII from our systems, please send an email with your specific request to support@videoschoolonline.com. We will work with you to make any corrections deemed necessary. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. Additionally, note that registered Instructors and Students may change visibility of their respective personal information throughout our website by editing their personal profiles.

If you provide your email address to Video School Online, you will always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving email newsletters and promotions through the unsubscribe link in the email communications or by logging into and changing the preferences for your user account. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a credit card processing partner) before you changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change your preferences directly with that third party.

**Our Policy Concerning Children**

As stated in our Terms of Use, our website and services are offered and available only to you if are 18 years or older, or if you are between 13 and 18 years old and have obtained the consent of a parent or legal guardian prior to accessing the website, registering an account, or using the services. If you do not meet this eligibility requirement, you may not use our website or services. Video School Online does not knowingly collect or store any personal information from or about children under the age of 13. We will delete such information if we become aware that it has been submitted through our website. Parents or legal guardians who believe that Video School Online might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13 may submit a request to [support@videoschoolonline.com](mailto:support@videoschoolonline.com) and request that such information be removed.

**Securing Your Information**

Video School Online takes a range of security measures designed to protect your PII and keep it confidential (unless it is non-confidential by nature) and free from any unauthorized alteration. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of financial information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. As the safety and security of your information also depends on the precautions you take, we ask you not to share your password with anyone.

**Third Parties and Other Information Collectors**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties through our website, whether between Instructor and Student or other Users or individuals, different rules may apply to their use, collection, and disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. Since we do not control the information use, collection, or disclosure policies of third parties, you are subject to their privacy policies.

Our website may include links to third party websites. Once you have used these links to leave our website, you should note that we do not have any control over third party websites. We are not responsible for the content of such websites or the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. Third-party websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policies applicable to the websites in question.

**Do-Not-Track Procedures**

Note that any Do-Not-Track instructions from your browser or similar mechanism will not affect our collection of the data that you voluntarily provide to Video School Online through such means as browsing our website, signing up for any of the Services or any Courses, entering PII into information fields on our website, or posting on any of our forums or blogs. Be advised that third parties are free to collect any information that you volunteer to Video School Online that is visible to the public. Therefore, please do not provide Video School Online with any information that you do not want collected.

**California Civil Code Section 1798.83 Compliance**

Under California law, upon request Video School Online is required to disclose to its California customers the identity of any third parties to whom we have disclosed PII within the previous calendar year, along with the type of PII disclosed, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Please note that under California law, we are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, email us at support@videoschoolonline.com.

**Users Outside of the United States**

The Sites are hosted in the United States and are governed by the laws of the United States. If you are using the Sites outside the United States, please be aware that your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where Video School Online’s servers and databases are located. By using the Sites, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence.

**No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may review and update this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. It is the responsibility of Users to keep abreast of those changes. All changes are effective immediately when posted. As such, your continued use of the Sites or Services after Video School Online makes changes to this Privacy Policy is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this webpage periodically for updates. In addition, Video School Online will notify Users of any material or significant changes to this Privacy Policy relating to the way in which we use your personal information by placing a notice on the Sites and notifying registered Users via email.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:

Video School Online, Inc.

PO Box 4766

San Dimas CA 91773

Email: support@videoschoolonline.com

## Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use

### 1\. Terms

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

### 2\. Use License

  1. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Company’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: 
    1. modify or copy the materials;
    2. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
    3. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Company’s web site;
    4. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
    5. transfer the materials to another person or ‘mirror’ the materials on any other server.
  2. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Company at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
  3. Video School Online Inc. has the right to terminate any course membership at any time, for any reason. ‘Lifetime’ access to a course (one time purchase; subscription; or payment plan) refers to the ‘life’ of the course or website.

### 3\. Disclaimer

  1. The materials on Company’s web site are provided ‘as is’. Company makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Company does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

### 4\. Limitations

In no event shall Company or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Company’s Internet site, even if Company or a Company authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

### 5\. Revisions and Errata

The materials appearing on Company’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Company does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Company may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Company does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

### 6\. Links

Company has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Company of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.

### 7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications

Company may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

### 8\. Governing Law

Any claim relating to Company’s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of New York without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
